Listen, Dear,
staying alive is all that matters.
You've watched those
Bollywood movies, right?
When the cops close in,
even the hero can't escape,
so what chance do you have?
1990, ALLAHABAD
You've got to make up
for your own karma.
But for that,
you've got to stay alive.
I'm warning you...
For one more time.
If you don't follow, we'll open fire.
This is your last chance.
Drop the gun and come out, now.
Nobody's going to shoot!
Put the guns down!
Come on out, Dear!
I'm counting to three.
One...
He won't do it.
Kishan, take the shot.
Nice one, buddy.
You just earned yourself
a medal this Republic Day.
I'm grateful to you, sir!
God bless. Well done.
Are you just gonna smile,
or go have a look?
You want me to go take a look?
- Who fired the shot?
- Me.
Then should I call
your father to confirm it?
Just go!
Yes, sir.
Dear God! Help me!
Open fire!
2 YEARS AGO,
1988 ALLAHABAD
ALL TRUCKS BELONG TO MAALIK
What's in the truck?
Just sand.
Show your license and registration.
Come down.
Are you deaf or what?
Can you count?
Start counting.
All 50 trucks belong to Maalik.
Guess you didn't hear me, huh?
- What are you doing?
- Come down!
- Let go of me!
- I said, come down!
This ain't right.
You're going to teach
me what's right and wrong now?
Trust me,
these trucks belong to Maalik.
- You'll regret this!
- You...
What's going on here?
He tried to threaten me
when I asked for the papers, sir.
Said all 50 trucks belong to Maalik.
All 50 trucks belong to Maalik?
He wouldn't listen.
Even slapped me!
He told you they're Maalik's trucks,
- then why'd you stop him?
- But sir...
Why?!
And you slapped him too?
He's getting cocky just
because of that uniform!
Getting cocky, huh? Stopping
his trucks and hitting his men too?
These are Maalik's trucks, right?
Who do they belong to? Maalik!
- Maalik's trucks, he says!
- Why're you hitting me, Inspector?
- Stop hitting me!
You'll regret this!
Inspector...
Round them all up.
- Make them kneel.
- Round up everyone!
Get up.
Is this a party or what?
What are you waiting for?
Christmas?
Hey...
What's going on?
Did you stop the trucks, sir?
- Yeah.
- Why?
Do I need your permission?
Can't you see this is a checkpost?
I see the checkpost,
but our trucks never
get stopped before.
Why? You all think
you're royalty or something?
Didn't you warn him?
We run this town, sir.
But I guess you're new here.
If you insult an officer on duty,
I'll have you kneel with the rest.
What's with the death stare, huh?
What are you staring at, huh?
These are Maalik's trucks, Inspector.
No officer ever dared
stop them before.
But you did.
I'm just trying to figure
out if you're brave...
or just plain stupid.
Stand up straight.
Don't faint on me.
Who's going to pick you
up if you fall, huh, fatty?
Help!
Let me go!
Come on, get the car.
For that little stunt, baby elephant,
you deserve a reward just as big.
Move it.
- Throw him in the car.
- Come on, Inspector.
- Let me go!
- Stop yelling.
- Get moving.
- I said, let me go!
Quit shouting.
Right, Inspector?
Greetings, Boss!
Where's Maalik?
- Probably sleeping.
- Where?
I'll have to go look.
Got a new catch.
Wake him up.
He's on Neeraj's roof.
Maalik.
Dadda.
Badauna's here.
And he brought an inspector with him.
What time is it?
3 o'clock.
Make some tea.
I'm coming.
Remember the day you were born?
Birthday?
When is that big day?
15th August, 1947.
This guy showed up when
the whole nation got its independence!
Ask him, Tripathi...
Was he born, or just something
the British left behind?
I see trouble in your
stars - especially Saturn.
Tried any fixes?
Won't you even
let me sleep peacefully, Badauna?
Got a new catch.
He stopped our trucks.
Not getting your cut on time, Officer?
No one told me those
trucks were Maalik's.
If I had known,
I never would've stopped them.
Liar!
Oh, you “didn't know”?
Then what made you strip
them and beat them to a pulp?
Forgive me, Maalik.
Forgiveness isn't an option, Officer.
You stopped Maalik's trucks
knowing exactly who they belonged to.
Who'd you sell your
loyalty to this time?
Maalik, I'll release
all the trucks right now.
That you will anyway.
Answer the damn question.
We don't ask twice.
Chandrashekhar.
Chandrashekhar!
So, Officer,
sure, you had orders,
but you went through with it anyway.
What do you think folks
will say if we don't react?
“That Maalik's slipping.”
Have mercy on me, Maalik.
I've got two little kids.
My parents are old.
There's nobody to look after them.
I swear...
I swear I won't ever do it again.
Your words don't mean squat here.
You've got to pay for what you did.
It's the law of nature.
And if it's not,
Maalik will make it the law.
Got it?
Forgive me this once.
I'll do whatever you say.
If you want,
I'll even lick my own spit!
Do it.
What?
Lick your spit!
Ohh!
Again!
Imagine this...
After 8.4 million lifetimes,
you finally get born as a human
and this guy wastes
it licking his own spit.
- As long as sun and moon will gleam,
- Balhar Singh's glory all will sing!
What brings you here, Chandrashekhar?
Two years back,
when you were begging for votes,
I was right there with you,
not Maalik.
You don't get rid of
a guy like him overnight.
- It takes time.
- Time, huh?
I try to get the railway contracts,
and he just swoops in, waving his gun
and takes them from right under me.
He's hauling truckloads
of sand from the river,
and the officials won't do
a thing because they're scared stiff.
Just last night...
he made an Inspector
lick his own spit before killing him.
Yeah, I know.
Wait till the Corporation elections--
Do you think I'm some fool?
It's always Parliament, Municipal,
or some block-level election.
You keep running for office,
and we're stuck tagging along,
shouting your slogans...
- As long as sun and moon will gleam,
- Balhar Singh's glory all will sing!
Look...
if you can't handle this guy,
just say so now.
I'll deal with it myself.
You know I'm not exactly gentle.
Just calm down. I'll take care of it.
Trust me, I will.
- As long as sun and moon will gleam,
- Balhar Singh's glory all will sing!
- Long live...
- Balhar Singh!
He's such a pain in the neck.
Now I've got to cook up
a new bully just to take him down.
Pardon my bluntness, sir,
but you're sitting on
a ticking time bomb here.
If that thing goes off,
your reputation's going
to come crashing down in flames.
There's only one way to handle this.
What's that?
There's a guy in Lucknow.
Suspended for three years.
Done 98 encounters.
Prabhu Das.
The bully with a license to kill.
Look, I'm not here to
scare you or your family.
Check under the bed.
I know you have nothing
to do with Maalik.
But you should be worried
about me showing up.
Otherwise, this whole trip
would've been pointless.
Deepak hasn't come here
in the past two years, sir.
Sir... you don't get it.
We're just simple farmers.
Simple farmers, huh?
That was before, Bindeshwar ji.
Not anymore.
Now, you're the father of the
notorious criminal they call Maalik.
Sir, your tea.
Want some?
If you make tea like this again,
I swear, I'll break your arms.
Get lost!
What's going on here?
Why are the police here?
Everything's a total mess.
Hello, ma'am.
I've got to say,
you raised one hell of a son.
The guy's got everyone
shaking in their boots.
- What?
- Open it.
Sir...
Sir, please...
Listen to me.
Please...
Not in here.
Please don't go in here, sir.
I'm begging you.
Don't do it.
I've got nothing
but respect for elders
but please,
don't stand in the way of the law.
Isn't she your daughter-in-law?
Yes.
What kind of man is he?
Doesn't even come to see his own wife?
What's your name, dear?
Shalini.
Prabhu Das, that's my name.
I've chalked up 98...
I've got 98 encounters under my belt.
I was chilling in Lucknow,
when the government ordered me to head
to Allahabad as I was needed there.
You want to know why I got transferred
here as the SP of Allahabad.
To take out your husband,
Maalik aka Deepak.
Do me a favour, will you?
Tell him I've saved a
spot for him in Allahabad Jail.
He'll live if he surrenders.
If he doesn't...
You won't look too
good as a young widow.
I just really don't
want to kill people.
But I can't help it,
it comes with the job.
God bless.
Who is it?
It's me.
Seeing me makes you so upset
that it makes you cry?
Should I leave?
Looks like you jinxed me--
He stormed into my room.
Told me to ask you to surrender.
I've come too far, Shalini.
There is no surrender at this stage,
Things get worse.
So what now?
You're just going
to keep running forever?
Just a few more days.
Once I secure that Assembly seat,
I'm legit, and we'll be cruising
around like VIPs in official cars.
Is that so?
And when is that
day going to come?
Soon.
Don't be scared of the police.
They talk big,
but not all of them bite.
Father's worried.
Well, with a son like me,
trouble becomes part of the legacy.
I don't like being away from you.
Same here.
Everything I'm doing is for you.
And this dimple of yours.
Deepak.
Yeah?
It's father.
Damn it. Guess he's not
going to let me become a father.
The police stepped foot here
yesterday for first time ever.
God bless you.
And that was the last time.
They are not coming back.
Deepak... you must surrender.
Look at what you've become.
Maalik...
that's what I've become!
What else was I supposed to be?
Why won't you understand?
One day,
the police will shoot you down.
Don't get so worked up.
You'll age before your time.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Always worried about you.
The whole state's worried about me.
You're my mother.
You gave birth to a brave son.
I'll be fine.
I said I'll--
Everyone,
tell my mom that I'll be fine.
He'll be fine, Aunty.
Louder. With respect.
He's going to be fine, Aunty.
Come on, Mom.
Brother... the police
have entered the village.
Deepak...
Police.
See you, Uncle.
Goodbye, Uncle.
Can you count?
Start counting then.
- One...
- Two.
- Three...
- Four.
- Five...
- Six.
Seven...
Come on, Inspector, you know you
should've brought an army to face me.
But instead, you've got
these six fragile officers.
Are you trying to insult me?
- No, Maalik. I...
- Listen, Inspector,
your SP barged into
my home yesterday.
I'm enough pissed off to
bury you and your jeep in
the ground without a second thought.
We made a mistake.
We'll turn the car around and leave.
We won't come back.
Smart boy.
Badauna.
Give them 1400 rupees.
Two hundred each.
Have fun.
Maalik, you don't have to do that.
There's no need.
Get lost.
Let's go.
Hey Manoj, cue the sound.
Perfect!
Amazing...
Here he comes.
- Is that him?
- Yes.
Hey, lawman.
Who, me?
You get paid to serve the people,
or just keep your officers happy?
Whose kid is this?
He's the SP's grandson.
- Prabhu Das ji's grandson?
- Yes.
Such an important person, and you're
the one fetching him from school?
What if someone snatches
him on the way home?
You don't even carry a gun.
Haven't you heard of Prabhu Das ji?
Who would dare?
Have you heard of Maalik?
What happened, son?
Did you shit yourself?
It stinks real bad.
Hello, son. What is your name?
Debu.
- Debu, you want a lollipop?
- Yes.
- Want more?
Come on, get in the car.
Come on. Let's go.
Here... have some snacks.
Buzz off!
Get him some lollipops.
Who was on duty?
Who was on duty?!
I ASKED, WHO WAS ON DUTY?!!
Where do you think
you're going, huh?
Rascal...
Sir. Sir... you'll hurt him, sir.
Forgive him, sir.
You'll kill him!
Please, sir. Stop, sir.
Sir...
Come on, Das Babu...
This is not fair.
You come all the way to my city,
just to catch me.
Wouldn't it be strange
if I didn't pay you a visit?
Where is my grandson?
Badauna.
Come on, Debu.
He's so fluent with his English poems:
Twinkle-Twinkle Little Star and all that!
You know he dreams of being
just like you when he grows up?
So I thought,
I must meet this great man.
Go inside.
Hey, Rasgulla...
My glasses.
Look at that!
A cop's grandson,
thinking he owns the world.
How dare you lay
a hand on my grandson?!
No, no, no.
I should be asking you that.
How dare you storm into my house?!
You threatened my parents,
and you made my wife cry.
These are more than enough reasons
for me to spill someone's guts!
But for now, I'll let you live.
Because your grandson adores you.
Because he respects you.
And I thought a warning
would be enough for the first time.
Next time, remember to see
your grandson's face
before you storm into
my house again.
You'll storm into my house there,
and I'll be out here telling
your grandson tales
of your "greatness."
This is my last warning
I heard you've got
98 encounters to your name.
Then you must be a man.
So why don't you face me like one?
Out in the open.
It'll be fun.
What are you standing there for?
Get lost!
Hey Brother, how are you doing?
A man who's running the show is
asking me how I'm doing? That's cute.
Come on, I'm just a
low-level government employee.
I'm in no position to run any show.
Is that so?
Then how did the Simariya Bridge tender
get approved before it went public?
The tender would've been made
public if the orders came from above.
The top brass called the shots.
What could I do?
Tell me about it!
Now Maalik's going to
build roads and bridges too?
Then what are we
businessmen supposed to do?
It's got me concerned too.
If the tender had been made public,
I would've made a few bucks off it too.
A total loss for me.
If you're at a total loss, why don't
you do something about it, Ram babu?
You do it and I'll
you lend my support.
Simple.
Ram Sevak Gupta.
He handles all the road and
construction business for Maalik.
- Move!
- Get lost!
- Madam, please let me through--
- Gupta!
No...!
Will he not let me live in
peace until he's out of the picture?
Tell him to stay off the grid.
I'll let him know when
it's safe to come out.
And tell him to stay calm.
No drama.
Sir, you've been summoned.
Maalik is calling you.
What the--
Guess we'll have to interrupt
Dadda's sleep today.
Let's go, Dadda.
Greetings, Dadda.
- Live long.
- Only if your men let me.
Come on, Balhar Singh,
are you really that scared of
me that you had to bring Dadda along?
Your anger's misplaced.
I'm not a fool.
I see everything.
Dadda, Prabhu Das was transferred
to Allahabad overnight.
What for?
He barged into my home
as soon as he joined duty.
He barged into your
daughter-in-law's room!
I'm not here to be a goon.
I'm here to do business.
The Simariya Bridge tender?
My guy got it.
- Didn't he?
- Yes.
Chandrashekhar stormed into
the cinema hall and shot him.
Violence in entertainment...
imagine that!
With his blessings, of course.
There you go again.
I'm on your side.
Why would I do such a thing?
Look...
I don't know Chandrashekhar,
but I know you, Maalik.
I may not be able to reason with you,
but I can at least make a request, right?
You want to do business?
Go ahead.
But do it by the book.
Everyone knows tenders
get approved using power.
But flex your muscles
after the tender goes public.
Do it before, and you'll just hurt the
other businessmen's sentiments, right?
Dadda, I'm not here to
entertain these businessmen.
If they want entertainment,
they can go watch a
good movie in the theatre.
If they want to do business
with a gun to one's head,
then I'm not exactly
packing a water pistol.
I can shoot back too.
Come here, Dadda.
Please.
Dadda, I'm under a lot of pressure.
If you have a problem with me,
come talk to me directly.
You are like a father to me.
Talk some sense into him.
He won't have his ass glued
to that Legislator seat forever.
And if he does,
I know exactly how to peel it off.
Chandrashekhar killed my guy.
I've been searching high and
low for him, but can't find him.
Where are you hiding him?
I found out Ram Babu tipped him off.
So I killed him.
I'm keeping the body in your car.
Deliver it to his family.
He has two little kids who
are now orphans because of you.
So make sure you announce a 200,000
rupee compensation for his death.
Be a good leader.
You're making me commit these sins.
Take care of your ass.
So long, Dadda.
Having fun?
When your doom is near your
mind turns irrational with fear.
You made him who he is,
and now he doesn't
even fear you anymore.
Eliminate him, Dadda.
Eliminating Maalik
is not a piece of cake.
I created him,
and I knew...
there's never been anyone like him,
and there never will be.
This game is full
of thrill and suspense.
Now all eyes are on whether
the duo of Deepak and Badauna
can lead their team to
victory once again this year.
Or will it be Hardoi
who takes the win?
It has now become
a three-on-one battle.
Only three minutes remain!
- Fast.. From Center.
- Hold the line
Come on.
Keep at it.
Weaving past the players,
Deepak swiftly drives the ball
forward toward the goalpost.
Deepak to Badauna.
Deepak moving closer to the goal...
Badauna, Ball!
Badauna's aerial football pass to Deepak!
Kick it...
It's in the air...
The ball's in the air!
A side kick from Deepak!
And it's a GOAL!
Allahabad's team is still
very much in this game.
Brilliant!
Wow, Deepak!
Deepak has completely
stunned Hardoi's defense!
Only three minutes left, Deepak.
We're down by one goal.
Work your magic.
- Take your position... positions, guys!- Could this be the moment
that changes the course of the match?
To your positions, fast.
Brilliant. Well played..
Deepak snatches the ball with brilliant skill!
Once again, he charges past Hardoi's players,
heading straight for the goalpost!
Deepak, pass the ball.
One man outplaying them all!
Deepak... the ball!
- Come on, Deepak, pass the damn ball!- Badauna calls for the pass from Deepak!
Pass it here!
Deepak...
Go for it! Score the goal!
Do it!
What is going on out there?!
Why didn't Deepak score that goal?!
He's brought doom upon himself!
It's a victory for Hardoi!
For the first time in three years,
Allahabad has been defeated!
What the hell, man?
You cost us the match.
No, I didn't.
I planned to lose from the start.
Planned to lose?
Your sister-in-law
is from "Hardoi".
She would've stopped
talking if we won.
You threw the match for a woman?
A woman sparked Mahayudha...
football's nothing by comparison.
You'll understand
once you get married.
Hey..
What happened?
Shankar Singh's here.
Shankar Singh's here. Come on!
I'm not coming.
- Long live...
- Shankar Singh!
Let me through!
Hey! Take it easy...
You know,
whenever I visit Allahabad University,
I see my reflection
in every student here.
Because this was the
age when Shankar Singh
was chasing his dreams right here,
at Allahabad University.
But fate had other plans.
My father was often unwell.
And seeing him in that condition...
I knew my future was heading
straight into darkness.
One day, I shared these
feelings with my father.
He seemed concerned at first,
but later...
he told me a story.
A story I still remember,
one that is etched in my mind.
There was a village fair,
and a boy was wandering around.
Suddenly, he looked up and saw
a red balloon soaring into the sky.
The boy rushed to the balloon seller
and said, "I want a red balloon."
The seller replied,
"That was the last red balloon,
and it's gone."
The boy started crying.
He said,
"I want a red balloon"
"because red balloons
soar into the sky."
Hearing this,
the balloon seller smiled.
Then he took a yellow balloon,
filled it with air,
and set it loose in the sky.
Next, he took a green one,
filled it with air,
and sent that up too.
And then a blue one.
The boy stared at the sky, amazed,
seeing that all the balloons
can soar into the sky.
Then that balloon seller...
gave him a piece of wisdom.
He said,
"Balloons don't soar
because of their colour."
"They soar because
of the air inside them."
Every student at Allahabad University
should have that "air" within them,
so they too can rise
and soar into the sky.
So... are you ready to soar?
We are!
Say it louder...
- Long live...
- Shankar Singh!
The rains have been good this year.
And we had a good yield too.
If God stays generous
till the harvest,
this year could help us recover from
the setbacks of the last 2–3 years.
Deepak, look who has
graced us with his presence.
Who is he?
He's my Maalik.
I work his fields.
Go on, touch his feet
and get his blessings.
If he's your Maalik,
you touch his feet, not me.
He's just a kid, Maalik.
Your son has no manners.
Right.
What are you doing?
What? You really need me to explain?
I don't feel like it.
Just leave me be.
I'm your husband, alright?
I threw away the
football match for you.
Don't stop me today.
So just because you're my husband,
you think you can touch me
whenever you feel like?
It's been over a week, and
you're still holding back. Not today!
I'm on my period.
I cannot do anything today.
Again? You just had them ten days ago.
And I got them again.
How do you get them every ten days?
Stop making excuses!
And what about all the excuses
you've been giving for months now?
What have I done?
I've been asking for new
clothes for the past three months.
Why should I do anything
for you when you do nothing for me?
What's that got to do with this?
Fine, I'll take you
shopping tomorrow, alright?
Now let's have some fun.
You can touch me only
after we've been to the market.
Pull harder, I am enjoying it!
- Leave me alone. No means no.
- Come on, just this once.
- No.
- Deepak!
What is it?
Why are you yelling like that?
When did you get crowned king, son?
What's going on?
You need to be king of
somewhere to act like this.
He is my Maalik.
It wouldn't have hurt
you to touch his feet.
Why, did your Maalik's feelings
get hurt when I didn't touch his feet?
Stop arguing.
You know what he said?
He said, "Your son has no manners".
He's right.
Why are you getting offended?
Why don't you get it?
A house thrives on work,
not fights.
And Maalik like him
provide that work.
I work for him now. Tomorrow,
maybe you'll be working for him too.
Speak for yourself, Papa.
You don't get to decide my future.
Your boss hasn't done us any favours.
You work hard for him.
But he'll toss you aside
the minute he finds someone better.
What's that supposed to mean?
Am I some servant?
Why are you offended by the truth?
You're the son of
a helpless man,
so stop pretending to
be someone else.
My destiny may have made me born
to a helpless father,
but you're destined to be a father
to a strong son.
- Bindeshwar ji!
Bindeshwar ji!
What happened?
Someone's running a
tractor through your field.
It's ruining the crops!
Who's doing this?
Maalik! What are you doing, Maalik!
The old geezer's here.
What are you doing, Brother?
- Why are you doing, Brother?
- Stop.
Please stop, Brother.
Please stop him!
What are you doing?
It's my harvest.
Please stop him.
He'll ruin all the crops.
These fields belong to my Maalik.
I have harvested them.
I'm just a poor man. I'll lose
everything. Please, stop him.
I beg to you, please stop him.
I will be ruined, Maalik!
Can't you hear me?
Maalik...stop him!
- Where is the emergency ward?
- On the left, sir.
Left?
How are you doing?
What happened?
They beat him without mercy.
My father was working
on your fields, right?
Who beat him up?
One of Shankar Singh's men, Langda.
Did you ask Shankar Singh
why he did this?
I had warned my father...
the worker always suffers
while the Maalik stays untouched.
Deepak, stop!
You'll only cause more trouble!
Don't do anything crazy, Deepak!
Get out of my way!
We'll get into more trouble, Deepak!
- Deepak, don't...
- Badauna!
- Shankar Singh!
- Let it go, please.
- Please, just let it go.
- Who is it?
- Shankar Singh!
- Keep your voice down.
Deepak, let him go.
Please, let him go.
Let him go.
What's going on?
I told you to let go of him.
Wait there.
Remember what you said?
Balloons soars because of
the "air" inside, not their colour.
But we can only rise
if you let us breathe!
Calm down, kid.
Who are you?
The guy you ran over
with a tractor in Bahadurpur...
He happens to be my father.
So?
That's not my problem.
Not your problem?
Your guy beat up my father.
Who else will help
me get justice if not you?
Me?
Whose father are
we talking about here?
Mine.
If you can't help your own father,
why should I?
You may leave now. Go on.
You were giving all these
motivational speeches back in college.
Saying you saw yourself
in the students!
And today when a student approached
you, you're trying to get rid of him?
I do see myself in the students.
But I'm not like you.
If anyone had laid
a finger on my father,
I'd deal with it myself!
I wouldn't be begging someone
like Shankar Singh for justice.
Move on.
There'll be consequences.
You're a real piece of work!
Just a minute ago, you were begging,
and now you're threatening me?
Believe me, I will kill that Langda.
Okay.
Go ahead, kill him.
And come back when you're done.
Cut the crap now.
Get out of here.
- I will kill him!
- Let's go, Brother.
Get lost!
- Let's go.
- And don't come back!
You okay?
Yeah, he just grabbed my collar.
I saw that.
- Pandit.
- Dadda.
Keep an eye on the kid.
Let's see...
if he actually goes through with it.
Why play with firecrackers like that?
One day it'll blow up in your face.
Balhar...
It's Diwali.
Go celebrate.
Take a drag.
You must be feeling good
after embarrassing yourself.
Shankar Singh wasn't wrong.
If I don't stand up for
my father, who will?
What do you mean?
I'm going to make
that Langda pay for it.
You'll make Langda pay,
like seriously?
Good God!
I'll do anything,
but I'll never be like him!
He starts blabbering
when he loses his cool.
- I'm not blabbering.
- Then what exactly are you doing?
I will kill Langda.
With what? A bullet?
A bomb? A gun?
Or are you relying on some
big-shot godfather behind you?
He says, he'll kill him!
If I use a bullet,
the bullet will get all the credit.
If I use a bomb,
the bomb will be the star.
I'm a farmer's son,
with strong arms.
I'll take him down with my bare hands
and make a name for myself.
Don't get ahead of yourself, alright?
You want Langda?
I'll tell you where to find him.
Come with me.
A child's gone missing.
His name's Bablu.
He's seven years old.
If anyone finds him,
please contact us. Thank you.
There he is.
Then I thought,
how the hell do I catch him...
Don't stop until I say so.
What do you want?
After I whacked him,
he didn't stop to look.
You stay out of this.
If he ever shows up again,
I'll give him a few more whacks.
You are unbelievable!
What's with the death glare?
Hey, I'm talking to you!
What are you staring at?
Hey!
Are you deaf or what? Hello!
Do I look like your dad, kid?
Nah, never seen anyone
with a crutch before.
What if I take it away, huh?
How are you going to walk then?
Do you have any idea who I am?
I should be asking you that.
Do you even know who I am?
The guy you ran over with
a tractor happens to be my father.
I see!
Heard that?
That old geezer survived.
Move.
Play it!
Come on, play it!
Deepak, don't...
"Let the history of Chambal echo loud,
why do the shackles keep you retrained and bowed?"
"Your feet are grounded, they never fly,
seek out the rebels, the bold and the wise."
"Think of the paths that call to your fate,
step beyond the chains before it's too late."
"He shoots partridge swift and clean,"
"Once the heater sets the scene."
"The theatre shakes with
roaring joy and screams,"
"Once the heater sets the scene,"
Deepak!
Don't be scared, Badauna.
I'm about to make a name for myself.
Tomorrow's headlines will read:
"Maalik gets revenge for his father."
Maalik?
So what if I wasn't
born a Maalik?
I can still rise up and become one.
"Maalik will rise, and all will see,
From today, he rules rightfully."
"He's the ace of spades, sharp and true,
The rest are rookies, nothing new."
"Maalik will rise, and all will see,
From today, he rules rightfully."
"He's the ace of spades, sharp and true,
The rest are rookies, nothing new."
DEEPAK AKA MAALIK IS CONTESTING ELECTIONS.
WHO WILL DARE TO STAND AGAINST HIM?
Where did I go wrong, Dadda?
I became the Legislator
with your blessings.
If I messed up,
just tell me and I'll sort it.
Are you out of your mind or what?
You really think
I'm supporting Maalik.
I have also just found out that
he's even running for elections.
Maalik needs to be stopped.
We can't let him
run for these elections.
You always come to
me when you're in a trouble.
You didn't even ask me
before bringing in Prabhu Das?
Or did you?
He's a crook, not some angel.
We'll have to deal with him,
sooner or later.
The sooner the better, right?
I don't know what's
right or wrong here.
But with this beef
between you and Maalik,
my position is decided already.
I've got to keep things
balanced on both sides.
But... I can only
lead one of you.
And that one...
is going to be Maalik!
Fine, Dadda.
Do your thing.
But just remember...
Today, you're leading him,
but tomorrow he'll be
the one who brings you down.
Badauna... why are you looking lost?
I'm just drawing a blank here.
If you were the smart one,
you'd be sitting in my chair
and counting all the cash.
Badauna, we can't keep
scaring people with guns forever.
There'll come a day when
no one's scared of them.
And the one with the power
and position then... will be Maalik.
And you think you can
get that power and position?
Winning these elections isn't
going to be a walk in the park.
Nothing has ever come easy for me.
But I'm set on doing this.
I've made up my mind,
and I'm going for it.
And I'm sure about it.
I've always stuck by you,
right or wrong.
Have I ever called you
out on your decisions before?
But today,
I feel that if you run for elections,
Allahabad's going to bleed.
There are two kinds
of people in this world.
Those who grind for every bite
and the ones who spill blood
to take what they think is theirs.
I'm the second kind.
I don't give a damn if people
call me a hero or a villain.
I'm the hero of my story.
If the hero gets everything handed
to him... where's the fun in that?
The hero looks the
best when he's fighting...
against the world,
people, and himself.
I've fought through it all so far
and I'll keep fighting.
Your friend's talking
like Amitabh Bachchan,
and you didn't even chuckle?
Hey, respect the cash.
Manoj!
Get dinner ready.
Shankar Singh's going to gain
the most if he wins the elections.
He'll become the uncrowned
king of Allahabad.
He'll use Maalik like a pawn.
And his first move will
be to take you out, Legislator.
Prabhu ji...
Thank you...
for dropping by and telling me
about my ‘bright future'.
Did I call you here
to swat the damn flies?!
Never in my life
has a criminal come to my house,
stared me down, and threatened me!
And I'm still doing my best.
Bullshit.
But he's always on the move,
and no one ever snitches on him.
How the hell am I
supposed to kill him?
Even if someone gives you a heads-up,
you still won't be able to take him out.
- Come again?
- He's right.
- What is he saying?
- You won't be able to kill him.
- But I...
- Nope.
These two are driving me crazy!
Speaking in Bengali
isn't helping anything.
- Sir...
- It can't be done.
Just tell me where
I can find him.
He's on Munna's roof.
Get out! Get out of here!
Get out of here now! Run! Run!
Tripathi's downstairs.
Who did this?
Prabhu Das.
He's surrounded us.
Prabhu Das!
Let's end this once and for all.
Deepak, this is
exactly what they want:
To rile you up so
they can take you out.
Now's not the time to go in
retalitate. Let's get out of here.
I've been attacked,
and you want me to just run?
Why don't you get it? You think
the cops showed up on their own?
Someone tipped them off.
Prabhu Das must've come prepared.
Let's go, Deepak. Move.
Come on, Deepak, let's go.
Damn it.
This way, Deepak.
Escape through the rooftop, Deepak!
Keep your eyes peeled.
How many did we lose?
Four of our guys got shot, Maalik.
We got the rest out the back door.
We'll deal with them
later, Deepak. Let's go.
Deepak!
Come on.
Let's go, guys.
I never thought it'd be
Neeraj in my wildest dreams.
If I'd known, I would've
dealt with him a long time ago.
Dealt with him?
Has anyone ever dared
to snitch on you before?
I think Prabhu Das
didn't get the memo.
Oh, he did.
I told him not to come near my house.
And he won't again.
If you ask me, Maalik,
let's just put a bullet
between that Balhar's eyes.
How many people are we going to kill?
Everyone's got a problem with Maalik.
So let's just take
out anyone who's a problem.
What?
What's your problem?
You are at home, and there
are other people living here too.
Leave your weapons outside.
And if you can't,
then don't come home.
Idiot or what.
Leave the weapons out immediately!
The boys are pissed,
forgive them.
My, my, my!
You can kill anyone with just a look.
Now, smile.
Just a little. Please.
I haven't really gotten
my complete share of happiness yet.
I'm just wondering, how long
this little bit of what I have left will last.
What do you mean by that?
It'll last as long as I'm here.
Is it?
And how long will you be here?
As long as you are.
It's just a game
of snakes and ladders.
Don't be scared.
It'll be over soon,
and we'll never have to look back.
You can play all you want.
I know, I cannot stop you.
But be careful of that snake at 99.
One bite,
and it's game over.
I've never seen the traders
in Allahabad in such a dire state.
You guys do all the work,
and Maalik takes the cake.
I get what you are trying to say,
but no one knows these
traders better than I do.
Like it or not, that's the truth.
No one can walk away from Maalik now.
Call it fear or call it loyalty.
Do you see what Maalik's
doing to you?
Unbelievable!
You guys risk your lives
to get the sand, and he's
the one raking in all the profit.
Iron goes for ten thousand a ton,
and what do you get?
Two thousand!
What does he get?
- Eight...
- Eight thousand...
Don't you get it? Someone's
taking your hard-earned money.
That's nothing new.
The powerful have always
controlled the markets!
It's been that way forever,
and it always will be!
It's never been this easy
for traders to get raw material.
- Is it?
- Who's protecting the traders?
Maalik.
You know the cops
are right on his tail?
He'll be dead sooner or later,
and then who's going protect you?
Only time will tell.
No, I'll tell you that!
My guy's taking over
here starting tomorrow.
I'll be the one buying
and selling raw materials!
Anyone who wishes to challenge me...
- Long live...
- Maalik!
In the upcoming
Assembly elections...
everyone here
must vote for Maalik.
Maalik's providing
every family with..
- a sack of grains,
- Suraj Yadav's here.
some sweets,
- and a blanket.
- He looks worried.
He's also going to build a school...
Maalik, you've got
to show up, just once.
Chandrashekhar's loading up all
the iron at the factory in his trucks.
He kicked our trucks out.
He's saying business is tough
since Ramsevak Gupta got killed.
Chandrashekhar's got his
people in Railways and PWD.
He's buying up all the
tenders by paying extra.
The cops are all over the place.
It's nearly impossible to get sand
and iron through the checkpoints now.
We're paying double what we used to,
and they're still seizing our trucks.
They are trying to
shut me down on purpose.
The elections are in eight months.
They want me to slip
up and give them an opening.
We've got to be play it safe.
How will that help, Deepak?
What if we play it safe and
they plot something else to trap you?
If you listen to me, let's show everyone
that Maalik's still in the game.
The traders have unshakable
faith in you, Maalik.
If you stay quiet, we'll
never get back on our feet again.
Who's at the factory?
Krishna Shukla.
Chandrashekhar's right-hand man.
No peace for a second.
Off you go!
Get him! Go grab him!
Make sure no one lives to tell the tale.
You are dead meat!
Run! Maalik's here!
We're being ambushed!
Shukla! Stop!
Damn you!
Stop...! How dare you
take over the factory, Shukla!
Don't let him escape! Get him!
Run!
Where do you think you're going?!
Stop!
Flank them from the other side!
Go, go, go! Don't let them slip!
Come on, pick up the pace!
Stop!
Come on!
"Let the history of Chambal echo loud,
why do the shackles keep you retrained and bowed?"
"Your feet are grounded, they never fly,
seek out the rebels, the bold and the wise."
"Think of the paths that call to your fate,
step beyond the chains before it's too late."
"He shoots partridge swift and clean,"
"Once the heater sets the scene."
"The theatre shakes with
roaring joy and screams,"
"Once the heater sets the scene,"
"BANG! BANG!"
"He shoots..."
"Once the..."
"BANG! BANG!"
"After falling for you,
I'm not the one I used to be,"
"Now I wait down your lane,
clutching my heart anxiously."
"Now I'm uncertain of where I'll be,
night or day,"
"As I wait down your lane,
clutching my heart anxiously."
"Make me yours or I'll fade away,"
"Without you,
life has no meaning anyway."
"Make me yours or I'll fade away,"
"Without you,
life has no meaning anyway."
"I have no lack of lovers, you see,"
"Every heart beats just for me."
"Every heart beats just for me,"
"And yet...my silly
gaze is stuck on thee."
"I wait for you to say yes,"
"How will I hold my
heart in this distress?"
"I wait down your lane,
clutching my heart anxiously."
"Make me yours or I'll fade away,"
"Without you,
life has no meaning anyway."
"Make me yours or I'll fade away,"
"Without you,
life has no meaning anyway."
Everything that went down
in the last 24 hours
is really making the city look bad.
You guys need to sort
your issues face-to-face.
Bloodshed is not the way to go.
Elections are coming up.
Maalik!
- Yeah?
- Are you even listening?
I'm talking to you.
Violence is not the solution.
Elections are around the corner.
This is going to be
a problem for everyone.
Including...?
All of us.
Not me, though.
Ice cream.
Sixteen people are
dead in the last 24 hours.
Don't even try to blame me.
I was gunning for just one guy,
but he's so damn scared of me,
the second my name pops up, he freaks
out and hides in your damn pajamas.
I'm not scared of you.
If I knew where you were,
I would've ripped you apart.
Dadda, I can't stand
two kinds of people.
The ones who doesn't know
when to shut up,
and the ones who doesn't know
when to listen.
Maalik... let's find
a middle ground here.
That's why we're here.
Middle ground?
On your terms?
Alright, fine. I'll do it for you.
I've known you since
you had hair, Dadda.
I respect you.
I need your blessings.
But people call me Maalik.
I earned that name.
If anyone wants it,
they better earn it.
Why beg for it?
Who are you calling a beggar?
Who the hell are you
calling a beggar, huh?!
Hey...
Back off.
Let him go, Maalik.
Maalik... I said, let him go.
Maalik!
Let him go!
Can't you hear me?
I said let him go, Maalik.
Maalik... let him go.
- Let him go.
- Stay out of this, Dadda!
Stay out of this, alright!
You invited me over, fed me...
that's all I can do for you.
I'm in charge now,
so I call the shots.
You either get on board,
or get out!
Same goes for you.
Don't forget who you're talking to.
I'm not the only
one who should remember.
You better not forget
you're talking to Maalik!
I'm running for elections
and I'm going to win.
You can do whatever you want.
You got lucky this time.
Next time, don't count on
luck to bail you out.
Move!
I told you he'll take you
out too if he gets the chance.
This is just the preview.
Wait for the full show.
- Alright, fine. Let's go.
- You can't do this alone.
We need to team up.
Let's take him out together.
I've got your back.
He should not make
it out alive this time.
Top priority right now is figuring
out if Maalik's in Allahabad.
If he is, we make sure
he doesn't get out.
If he's not, we make sure
he can't get back in.
CRPF will be on every checkpoint
around the Allahabad border.
His house, the Trade Association,
the market and everywhere possible...
We'll have plainclothes policemen
and your guys watching all of it.
The coordination should
be seamless from both sides.
You see anything shady, don't wait,
shoot first, ask questions later.
Instill fear and get the
message out to the truck drivers
that no one's hauling Maalik's goods,
not even one load.
We're not arresting
anyone tied to his gang.
Those scums go down on the spot.
I'll head to the DRM office.
Maalik's guys will stir
up trouble because of the tender
and that'll be my cue to start shooting.
Chandrashekhar, you take
over the Trader's Association.
That's where Maalik's
election money is coming from.
Cut that off,
and he starts to fall apart.
Maalik's hopping around,
changing spots every day.
Make sure people are too scared
to even think about helping him.
Nobody should even be
thinking about elections.
If anyone's who gives
Maalik or his men shelter...
This is my area.
My family's been building
it up for generations.
No way Maalik's walking in
to enjoy the fruits of our work.
They will be face legal actions.
He made me struggle
for ground in my own backyard!
Maalik...
Make sure he's completely
crushed and under our control!
The whole damn city's
become a battlefield.
Cops are everywhere.
We've got nowhere to hide.
Can you believe this?
They stormed Suraj Yadav's
house and wiped out his whole family.
Father, son, everyone,
they didn't spare a soul.
Now there's talk in the Association
that Maalik's finished.
People are saying everyone's
carrying semi-automatics now.
Just think about that!
How are they even getting
their hands on those?
Got to be the cops.
Who else?
You don't get their game.
The cops can't handle it.
Chandrashekhar gave
it a shot and blew it.
So Balhar Singh, that Legislator...
flipped the whole thing
into a hit squad targeting me.
Then we take out Balhar Singh first.
What do you say?
- Semi-automatics?
- Yes, Maalik.
Call Naresh in Banaras.
I want all our guys
armed with full automatics.
Bang-bang-bang!
Full automatic!
Show me what you've got.
Try this one.
Beautiful.
Well done, Tripathi.
AK-47s, AK-56s, and German pistols.
All automatic.
- Pappu.
- Yes, Brother?
Take the backdoor with
Panu and Panditji.
The rest will storm
in through the front door.
- Okay, Brother.
- Okay.
We can't give Balhar Singh
a second to get away today.
Screw Balhar Singh.
Deepak,
you really think that idiot
could plan all this himself?
Show me.
What's the difference...
between a 47 and a 56?
AK-56 fires in bursts.
So does the 47.
So what's the actual difference?
You'll know when you
pull the trigger.
Which one looks better in my hand?
AK-56, Maalik.
Awesome.
Balhar Singh isn't dying today.
Then?
Let's go.
Crazy lunatic.
Deepak!
Brother...?
Shoot like there's no tomorrow.
Make this day unforgettable forever.
"The sound of bullets
echoes through the city"
Go. Hide.
- What's going on?
- I said GO!
Maalik...
Shankar Singh.
Maalik!
Light them up!
Finish them off, every last one!
End their game!
Check over there!
Dadda!
Come on, Dadda...
Dadda...
I'm like a father to you.
You are...
but you're not my father, Dadda.
You want to kill me?
Come on.
Kill me.
What are you waiting for?
Shoot.
Just do it, son!
I am your father.
You hear me?
A father never betrays
his son, Dadda.
Maalik...
Hmm?
Wake up.
What is it?
Sister-in-law's here.
Who?!
Sister-in-law... she's waiting downstairs.
How are Mom and Dad?
They have me.
They are doing fine.
They are just worried about you.
Worry makes you suffer twice.
Tell them not to worry.
You know... people are
saying some weird stuff.
I'm scared.
What kind of stuff?
That they are going to kill you.
Shalini, no one on
this earth can kill me.
Don't be scared.
Nothing's going to happen.
What if it does?
How could it?
I said I'll be fine.
Why don't you leave
the city for a few days?
If I leave now,
people will say Maalik's scared.
And I don't run.
That's weird.
So you're worried about what
people will say, but not about me?
Oh, my, my!
I'm doing all this for you.
Then why don't you leave for my sake?
Come back once things settle down.
You're scared for no reason.
Nothing's going to happen.
And I pray it doesn't.
But what about my fear?
It's stuck deep in my heart.
Hey fear!
Get out of Shalini's heart right now!
Don't make me come
in there and smash you!
The fear got scared.
Happy now?
You think all this is funny?
I did everything you asked.
You said we've got to live apart,
so I did.
But now I'm asking you
a small favour.
Please leave.
Can't you do this for me?
I'd give my life for you,
but I can't leave this city.
Why are you crying?
I didn't marry you
to make you cry, did I?
When it was just us,
I wasn't scared.
But now there's
a third life on the line.
It's only natural to be scared.
Third life?
Who is this third person?
Should I get my AK-56?
What?
Oh, God!
Badauna!
Send a word to Naresh
that we're coming tomorrow!
Tell him to find a good place to stay.
Your sister-in-law's
coming along as well.
Oh, this is fantastic news!
For news like this,
I'd even be down to move to Mars!
Have you started puking yet?
No worries, you will, sooner or later.
"It's impossible, can't you see?"
"Without you,
my very being ceases to be."
"It's impossible, can't you see?"
"Without you,
my very being ceases to be."
"These unsaid promises,"
"For you and me alone to bear."
"Without you,
nights feel like illusions,"
days lose all their meaning fair."
"It's impossible, can't you see?"
"Without you,
my very being ceases to be."
"For your sake,
there's so much I'd do,"
"I want to paint your
dreams with colours of dew."
"You can test me if you choose,"
"I'll pass through every
trial and never lose."
"You don't need to
prove your love to me,"
"All I need to see,"
"Is that you stay
close and by my side."
"Don't take your face
away from my longing eyes."
"It's impossible, can't you see?"
"Without you,
my very being ceases to be."
What are you thinking?
These last few days with you
felt like a whole lifetime.
I want that for the rest of my life.
Once I win the elections,
we'll travel like other government
officials, proud and loud.
And if I say I don't want that?
What do you mean?
Can I ask you for a favour?
Have I ever said no?
Swear on me.
Say it.
Surrender.
Are you out of your mind?
Surrender? Me?
Years of respect, glory... you
want me to just throw it all away?
How long you going to
think just about yourself?
Have you ever thought about me?
I'm doing all this for you, Shalini.
If I surrender now,
what'll I tell my kid?
"Your dad was worthless!"
"He got scared and surrendered!"
And what'll you say if you don't?
"The whole state's
scared of your father."
"You're Maalik's kid,
do whatever you want!"
"No worries, no fear!"
When the kid's born,
people will say,
"That's a criminal's child!"
Is that what you really want?
I earned this respect.
You earned only fear.
You can't even tell
respect and fear apart.
I don't want to live
scared all the time.
And I don't care about
power or luxury either.
You're the only family I got.
I just want my husband,
the guy who leaves for work in the
morning and comes home to me at night.
A husband I can stay with,
eat with, walk with,
and spend my life with without fear.
I want a normal life.
I never asked you for anything before.
But now, I'm serious.
Please, say yes.
Please surrender.
End this, once and for all...
Do it for me?
Listen...
Are you mad at me?
I could never give you
the happiness you deserved.
Lallan will take you home.
And you?
I'm going to do what you asked.
I'm surrendering.
You did what the big shots and
the whole damn police force couldn't.
It's true. No matter how
powerful a man becomes,
he still got to answer
to his wife.
I'll probably be in
jail a couple of years.
I can't survive that
long without seeing your face.
And I heard jail food
tastes like cardboard.
So when you come to visit,
bring me something decent.
Once I'm out
I'll be whoever
you want me to be.
We'll walk through Allahabad
with our heads held high.
I want a daughter.
With cute little
dimples like yours.
Come on, Badauna,
time for a fresh start.
Now I get how one woman
triggered the Mahayudha.
Good thing you figured
that out before getting married.
Once we're out of jail,
I'll get you married off.
Get lost.
Who'd want to marry me?
Who wouldn't?
How about Pandi? Marry him?
We'll dress him up as a
bride and get you two hitched!
Seriously?
You couldn't think of anyone else?
Someone else?
Manoj!
He's a great cook.
Can wear a sari better
than most women.
And you'll get some extra
room to spread the love.
Will you marry him?
It's a yes from me.
Where you going to
place the flowers, my dear?
It's a barren desert here!
If Badauna says yes,
I'll tie it to my
beard and dance for him.
You joker. I don't trust
your intentions.
Deepak.
Deepak ji.
- Brother...
- Deepak ji.
Oh yeah...
Totally forgot that's
what people used to call me.
Yes.
Once you sign this, you'll be
officially handed over to the police.
Okay.
So just sign here, Maalik.
Please.
I always heard the
law has a long arm...
didn't know it shakes this much.
Yes, right there.
What's wrong?
MAALIK!!!
- Move!
- Get out of the way!
- Give way!
- Move!
- Step side!
Move!
- Deepak! Deepak, no!
- "This love was a sacred tie,"
- Badauna!
- Control yourself! Deepak!
- "A lifelong responsibility we'd never deny."
- Let go of me!
"But just when it was time to try,"
"But you left without a goodbye."
"It's impossible, can't you see?"
"Without you,
my very being ceases to be."
They were Chandrashekhar's guys.
Hired from Bihar.
We're holding them
at the old Rest House.
We were told that Maalik
would be in that car.
Only after we opened fire
did we realise it was just his wife.
We screwed up.
It's a mistake.
And who's going to
pay for this ‘mistake'?
You've turned him into a rabid dog!
He's going to sniff us
out any second now and then--
I brought you in to handle him,
not to put my neck on the line!
He's damn well going to
shoot us right in our asses!
You should stay at
home for a few days.
I've beefed up the
security at your place.
No one's coming near.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
But I'm still a Legislator!
I'll have to step
out sooner or later!
- Then what?
- Then you tell me what do we do?
Let him have Chandrashekhar.
What do you mean?
Blame Chandrashekhar
for his wife's death.
Let them go face to face.
Maalik will take him out.
Then I'll show up, shed a few tears,
beg forgiveness, and wrap it all up.
But...
Chandrashekhar's one of us.
So?
You want me to take a bullet for him?
Just do what you are told.
Bringing you back was a mistake.
Should've left you suspended.
Completely useless!
Let's go.
Get it.
Shoot him on sight.
Brother...
Come on.
Here.
- Where is Maalik?
- I don't know.
Where the hell is Maalik?!
Tripathi...
Come on out!
Come out already!
Find him!
Come on out!
Come on out.
Chandrashekhar!
Come on out already!
Come on! Come on!
Did you find him?
Some Maalik, huh?!
Maalik!
Get up.
Father!
My son...
Maalik...
I can only imagine what
you're feeling right now.
Chandrashekhar totally had it coming.
Good riddance, I say!
He got exactly what he deserved.
He never took you seriously.
If you really think
I messed up, then...
go ahead and shoot me.
But Maalik, if I was in the wrong...
I wouldn't be standing
in front of you like this.
I came here because
I feel your pain.
I came to say,
I don't hold anything against you.
I never wished
anything bad for you.
I want you to rule.
You're like a brother to me, Maalik.
Just say the word.
I've got your back, no matter what.
You can run for elections...
rule however you want, and I'll
support you every step of the way.
You seriously think Chandrashekhar
was working for me?
Why would I work with him?
He was with Shankar Singh.
It was Shankar who
wanted you dead, not me.
Look, Maalik...
There's been a lot of
misunderstandings between us.
That's why I came...
to clear things up.
If you still want to kill me,
go ahead. I am unarmed.
What's going on?
What the hell just happened?
What happened, huh?!
What's going on?!
Maalik, police!
- Balhar Singh, you led the cops here?!
- No! I swear I didn't...
You snake!
Panu, go check outside.
On it.
Manoj!
- We got to move. Now!
- Let's go!
- Manoj!
- Let's go, Panditji!
Shoot him!
Shoot them all!
Shoot!
Let's go, Deepak!
Cover fire!
Run!
Come on!
Let's go, hurry!
Damn it!
Damn it! Run!
Damn it! Run! Run!
Police! Police!
This way, move it!
Keep going!
Bablu's dead!
Pappu!
Pappu's dead too!
Run! Run, Maalik!
Maalik, run!
Turn the car around!
Turn around, now!
Hey...
Pandit!
You're going to be okay.
Deepak, they've cleared
the whole damn village.
And we're almost out of bullets.
Pappu, Manoj, Bablu...
they're all dead.
We're going down swinging.
Let's take cover behind
the ruins.
Pandit, you okay?
- Maalik...
- You're going to be fine.
Nothing's going to happen to you.
This way.
Watch your step.
Go.
- You good?
- Yeah, I'm alright, Maalik.
Get up!
Let’s go!
Let’s go! Let’s go!
Deepak... this way!
Deepak!
Maalik!
Maalik, come on!
- Take positions!
- Okay, Maalik!
- We'll fight till the ammo runs out
- Yes, Maalik.
then deal with
whatever comes next.
Prabhu sir...
Maalik ducked into a corner
the moment I opened fire.
COME ON OUT!
Badauna... why?
What'd you say, Maalik?
Why?
Because everyone,
everywhere just keeps chanting -
Maalik! Maalik! Maalik!
Did you ever stop
to think what I wanted?
You'd always be "Maalik",
and I'd be what?
Your servant?
If Maalik says it's day, then it's day.
If Maalik says it's night, then it's night.
Maalik says,
"Badauna, go fight" and I fight.
Maalik says, "Badauna, go die"
and I just drop dead, right?
We fight together, we bleed together
and we rot in jail together too?
Why?!
Why should I go to jail for you?
You could've made me your heir.
But did you?
What did you say to me?
Yes...
"So what if I wasn't born a Maalik?
I can still rise up and become one."
I wasn't born Maalik either...
I can still rise up
and become one, right?
So, starting today...
I'm the Maalik of this place!
If you're going to kill me, Badauna
make damn sure I'm dead.
Because if I'm not...
I'll make sure that...
All you had to do was ask!
I would've given you everything!
But instead,
you brought the cops to take me out!
I didn't just bring
in the cops, though.
I even took down
Shankar Singh, Balhar,
and Chandrashekhar to be Maalik!
If you run for elections,
Allahabad's going to bleed.
You really think Balhar
Singh has the brains...
to hatch such a plan against you?
They were Chandrashekhar's guys.
Hired from Bihar.
- Balhar Singh, you led the cops here?!
- No! I swear I didn't...
I made sure nothing
stood in my way.
Please surrender.
End this, once and for all...
We were told that Maalik
would be in that car.
Only after we opened fire
did we realise it was just his wife.
You know what?
I got your Shalini killed!
Because I want to be
the 'King' of Allahabad!
Deepak, Deepak...
Deepak...
Remember I made you a promise
that you'd be the one
to take the final shot?
Well, I already hit him twice.
Maalik's almost dead.
What do you mean, "almost"?
Go and see it for yourself.
Badauna...
What do you mean "almost"?
It means he's still breathing.
So who's going to check?
SP sir, of course.
I'm not going
anywhere close to him.
When the cops close in,
even the hero can't escape,
so what chance do you have?
You've got to make up
for your own karma.
Go check!
Dear God! Help me!
OPEN FIRE!
Burn him alive!
END OF STORY
Now, we'd like to request...
Honourable MLA Mr. Badauna Singh,
to felicitate Mr. Prabhu Das,
for his outstanding service
in the police department.
With a huge round of applause,
please welcome Honourable
MLA, Mr. Badauna Singh!
SP sir...!
Finally retired, huh?
103 encounters... Not out!
Allahabad's never
going to forget that.
Don't think Allahabad
will forget you either.
Well done.
So... what's next?
A long vacation?
Back to square one.
Calcutta.
Come on.
A YEAR LATER
A YEAR LATER, CALCUTTA
"The sound of bullets
echoes through the city"
"He shoots partridge swift and clean,"
"Once the heater sets the scene."
"The theatre shakes with
roaring joy and screams,"
"Once the heater sets the scene,"
"He shoots partridge swift and clean,"
"MAALIK"
"Once the heater sets the scene."
"The theatre shakes with
roaring joy and screams,"
"MAALIK"
"Once the heater sets the scene,"
"Boots on his feet, Beretta in tow,"
"He shifts the mood,
wherever he goes!"
"Boots on his feet, Beretta in tow,"
"He shifts the mood,
wherever he goes!"
"No one dares to touch him,
not even death's throes,"
"Boots on his feet, Beretta in tow,"
"Maalik will rise, and all will see,"
"From today, he rules rightfully."
"He's the ace of spades,
sharp and true,"
"The rest are rookies, nothing new."
"Maalik will rise, and all will see,"
"From today, he rules rightfully."
"He's the ace of spades,
sharp and true,"
"The rest are rookies, nothing new."
"Let the history of Chambal echo loud,
why do the shackles keep you retrained and bowed?"
"Your feet are grounded, they never fly,
seek out the rebels, the bold and the wise."
"Think of the paths that call to your fate,
step beyond the chains before it's too late."
"He shoots partridge swift and clean,"
"Once the heater sets the scene."
"The theatre shakes with
roaring joy and screams,"
"Once the heater sets the scene,"
"He's not weak,
though born a labourer's son,"
"In his veins flows steel,
not just ordinary blood."
"Those who challenge his might,
Soon face the beast deep inside."
"All kings will fall silent with fright,
When he rises to claim the crown with pride."
"He's the ace of spades,
sharp and true,"
"The rest are rookies, nothing new."
"Maalik will rise, and all will see,"
"From today, he rules rightfully."
"He's the ace of spades,
sharp and true,"
"The rest are rookies, nothing new."
"The sound of bullets
echoes through the city"